blackoption.net 2017-12-25

# BlackOption - binary options without investments!

Website administration **http://blackoption.net** (the Site) respects the rights of users of the Site. We fully recognize the importance of privacy of personal information of visitors to our Website. This page contains information about what kind of information we receive and collect when You use the Site. We hope this information will help You make informed decisions regarding personal information provided to us. This privacy Policy applies to the Site and to information collected by this website and through him. It does not apply to any other websites and does not apply to websites of third parties which may be made links to the Site.

**1\. The collection of information**

When You visit the Site, we identify the domain name of Your ISP and country (for example, “aol.com”) and selected transitions from one page to another (so-called "activity stream crossings"). 

**1.1** The Information we collect on the Site, can be used in order to facilitate your use of the Website, including but not limited to: 

\- organization of the Site the most user-friendly way 

\- providing the opportunity to subscribe to the mailing list for special offers and themes, if You want to receive these notifications 

**1.2** The Site collects only personally identifiable information that You provide voluntarily when you visit or register on the Website. The concept of "personal information" includes information that identifies You as a specific individual, such as Your name or email address. Then how to view the contents of the Site without completing the registration procedure, You'll need to register to use some functions, for example, to leave a comment to the article.

**1.3** The Website uses "cookies" ("cookies") to create statistical reports. A cookie is a small amount of data sent by a web site that Your browser saves on the hard disk of Your computer. In "cookies" contains information that may be necessary for the Site - to save Your settings options to view and collect statistical information on Website, i.e. which pages You visited, what was loaded, the domain name of the Internet service provider and country of the visitor, and also addresses third-party web sites that refer them to the Website and beyond. However, all this information is not linked to You as an individual. "Cookies" do not record Your email address and any personal information about You. The technology is also on the Website uses the installed meter of company Spylog/LiveInternet/etc.

**1.4** In addition, we use the standard registers web server to count visitors and evaluate the technical capabilities of our Site. We use this information to determine how many people visit the Site and organize pages are the most user-friendly way, to ensure that the Site used browser, and make the content of our pages as useful as possible for our visitors. We record information on movements on the Site but not about individual visitors to the Website, so no specific information about You personally will not be retained or used by the Site Administration without Your consent

**1.5** To view the material without "cookies" You can set your browser so that it does not accept "cookies" or notify You of their premise (different, so we advise You to consult the "Help" section and figure out how to change the settings of the machine "cookies").

**2\. The sharing of information.**

**2.1** the Site Administration under any circumstances will not sell or give the use of Your personal information to any third parties. We also do not disclose Your personal information, except for the cases stipulated by the local laws.

**2.2** The website Administration has a partnership with Google, which puts on a reimbursable basis on the site pages promotional materials and ads (including, but not limited to, text, hyperlinks). In the framework of this cooperation site Administration shall communicate to all stakeholders the following information:

**2.1.1** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Website;

**2.1.2** Cookie Files promotional products DoubleClick DART uses the Google ads displayed on the Site as party AdSense for content.

**2.1.3** The Use by Google of the DART cookie enables it to collect and use information about visitors of the Website (except the name, address, email address or telephone number) about Your visits to Site and other web sites to provide the most relevant ads about goods and services.

**2.1.4** Google is in the process of collecting this information is guided by its own policy of confidentiality;

**2.1.5** Site Users can refuse the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google privacy policy for ad network of partner sites Google (http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**3\. Disclaimer**

Remember, transmission of personal information when visiting third-party sites, including partner companies, even if the web site contains a link to a Website or on the Website there is a link to those web sites are not subject to the terms of this document. Website administration is not responsible for the actions of other websites. The process of collection and transmission of personal information when visiting these sites regulated by the "Protection of personal information" or similar, located on the sites of these companies.
